Thank you for watching!
Today this could be the greatest day of our lives
Before it all ends
Before we run out of time
Stay close to me
Watch the world come alive tonight
Shine the light on our greatest days
Light up, light up, shine the light on our greatest days
Light up, light up
Tonight this could be the greatest night of our lives
Let's make a new start, the future is always too far
Can you see it? Can you see it? Can you see it in my eyes? Can you feel it? Oh, can you feel it? Can you hold it in your arms tonight?
Hi.
Hi, I'm Annie.
No?
You waiting for someone else?
All right.
Are you sure?
Hi.
Hello.
How are you?
Hi, I'm Annie.
Nice to meet you.
Very nice to meet you.
How you doing?
I'm doing well.
You?
I'm doing great.
Yeah?
Quite lovely.
You can sit right there, okay?
Mm-hmm.
All right.
I'll just go ahead and call you tomorrow.
Do you still like your family? Do they know you do this?
Mm-hmm.
They do? They're okay with it?
Yeah.
I'd be okay.
Does your family know you're here?
I hope not.
Hi, I'm Annie.
Nice to meet you.
Ricky.
Ricky?
Yeah.
Very nice to meet you.
I'll just sit right next to you right here.
Very cozy, right?
Pretty serious.
Yeah.
A lot of work, but you know.
That's right.
I'm here.
A hard worker.
Chill out and play with it, you know?
Yeah.
Well, we could go chill out in a private room.
All right.
Lucky number six.
My number.
Yeah.
Put up.
Some bad girl teach me lessons.
Hey.
Oh.
I'm a good girl.
Buy me presents.
I'm a bad girl, teach me lessons
Yeah.
Annie?
When Robert was here the other night, did he ask you for a dance?
Yeah.
And you danced with him?
Okay.
I'm everything you need
It was really weird.
Super weird.
Like, serial killer weird.
Yeah, like, he was like Indian Jeffrey Dahmer
and he kept rubbing my leg in a circle like that.
What is that? Is that a butterfly?
Yeah, it's a butterfly.
You're so classy.
I know.
I got dollar signs like a real hoe.
No, but you're manifesting with those.
He said I looked like his 18-year-old daughter.
And then he bought five dances from me.
That's fucking disgusting.
Well, at least he bought the dances.
Yeah.
You can touch me.
It's OK.
Yeah?
I'll build you a belt.
Yeah, make me a belt.
A money belt?
You don't have cash! Let's go to the ATM!
You want to go to the ATM, may I?
I can't spend too much.
Yeah, okay, let's go to the ATM.
Let's go get you some cash.
Okay.
Seriously, he came out of the bathroom one time
and he didn't zip up his fucking pants.
It's like, you can't zip up your fucking pants
after you take a piss.
I don't trust you with the music.
Dude, he's 40.
He's literally geriatric.
No, I know.
Annie, I got a kid who wants someone who speaks Russian.
You know, Jimmy, the girls and I have been talking,
and if your cousin doesn't start showing us some respect,
we're not gonna tip out anymore.
All right, I'll talk to him.
Who are you talking about, the DJ?
All right, seriously?
He's an asshole.
I shared my playlist with him,
and he was very rude and dismissive.
You're killing me.
Let's go. Come on.
No. I'm not eating my food.
That's why you have Tupperware. It keeps things fresh.
He's eating his food.
He's a spender. Come on.
Let's go time is money baby get a roll on it without friends without nothing and then some fucking
And then we keep it up. Okay. Hello. This is the beautiful annie
She's gonna take care of everything you need tonight
Annie make me proud
Yeah
I'm
I'm uh
Ivan
You can call me Vanya.
Vanya, okay. Nice to meet you.
And this is my best friend, Tom.
Hi, I'm Annie.
Yeah, not bad.
And you must speak Russian, right?
No, I don't speak Russian, but I know Russian.
What do you mean?
I can speak Russian, I just prefer not to.
but you can go ahead and speak Russian.
I'll understand.
I not understand. What the fuck?
Okay.
Yeah.
Hello.
My name is Annie.
I'm a Russian-speaking girl.
Stop!
No, my Russian is terrible. I can't even roll my eyes.
No, no, you are not bad, really. You are not bad in Russian. Your Russian is great.
Really? Okay, well, I disagree, so thank you.
Yeah. And how do you know Russian?
My grandmother never learned English, so...
Ah, uh-huh.
But enough about me. You two are from Russia.
Yeah, I'm from Russia. But he lives here, yeah.
Oh, so you're on vacation or...?
Yeah, vacation, I guess you can say that, yeah.
But I'm speaking, uh, on Russian, yeah?
Oh, yes, whatever you want.
Yeah, because my English sounds terrible at all, yeah.
No, no, no, your English is really good.
Yeah, and so I think we need to drink a bottle of alcohol for our shitty accents.
Yeah, and you wanna go to VIP, maybe?
Me too.
Yeah, excellent! I won!
Oh.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Yeah, it's a cool place,
and the room I'm bringing you to is really nice.
Mm-hmm.
Whoa.
You're very good, really.
And one.
Oh, yeah?
Thank you.
Where are you going?
No, I'm not going anywhere.
Can you sit on your hands for me?
What?
Sit on your hands? Hands under your legs.
Like...
Mm-hmm.
It's not allowed.
But I like you.
God bless America.
I don't want to be a loser and have money.
Um...
Give me your phone.
I'm sorry.
Yo.
Yo. Yo.
Did you pick up milk?
Do you see milk in the fridge?
No.
Then I didn't pick up the sucking milk.
Wonderful. Thank you.
Hi, um, I'm here for Mr. Zakharov.
Ivan?
Yeah, mm-hmm.
Hi, hello, what's up?
Hi.
Come in, come in, please.
So, welcome to my envelope.
Hugs.
Oh, yes, hugs.
Can I help you?
Oh, thank you.
You look beautiful, awesome.
First you want to drink?
Uh, yeah, I'll take a water.
Water? Are you sure?
You can take everything you want.
Vodka, tequila, whiskey, whiskey cola, Coca-Cola maybe?
No, a water is good. Yeah, thank you.
Suit yourself, Annie.
Sparkling or flat water?
Um, either is good.
Oh.
Wow.
Not too shabby.
What is shabby?
Oh, I'm just playing.
I meant your home is beautiful.
My home is okay, girl.
Sparkling.
Thank you.
Bedrooms, upstairs.
Let's go.
Okay.
Oh, sorry. I'm waiting for you.
Oh. Oh, hurry up.
They didn't make my bed yet.
Basti.
Whoa.
Nice view.
My view is better.
Okay. So, what are you looking for?
Um, sex?
Yeah, I know.
Any... like, anything special?
Yeah, special sex.
Special sex?
Okay. So, like, a little bit of everything?
A little bit of...
Yes, sounds like shit.
You want to take your clothes off?
Yeah.
Wow, okay.
You want to put this on?
Or do you want me to put it on for you?
Faster. Faster, faster.
Faster, faster, faster.
First step, step, step.
Okay, give me a stop.
Step, step, step.
It's...
Here.
Ah.
Want you.
Oh, uh, sure.
Sure, sure, sure, sure.
But be careful with that shit, yep?
Ah.
And that's for you.
Thank you.
Yeah.
It's very generous.
And I want to say one more thing.
Yes.
It was really amazing.
I love these guys.
Do you know them?
No.
Oh, you must know them.
So, um, how old are you?
21. How old are you?
Older than you.
No, I'm 23.
Oh, well, yeah, like...
Okay.
You're funny.
Yeah, I know.
Oh, what's up?
Funny, what?
I don't know.
You just, you're like, you're funny.
Funny, cool, right?
Yeah, of course.
Really funny, cool.
And if you don't mind me asking,
like what do you do to get all of this?
Oh, what do you think I do?
Well, what do you think I think you do?
Oh, fuck in English.
Okay, I can tell you, but it's a really big secret.
Okay.
I'm really big drug dealer.
Oh, really?
You trust me?
No, but I'm really big gun dealer.
Come on, oh my God.
Wait, so like you made some app or something?
Is that...
Yeah, yeah.
I made...
I have a couple of good ideas, but no, no, I know.
Okay.
My father.
Yeah?
In short, okay, my father is Nikolai Zakharov.
Sorry, I don't know who that is.
Google him.
Google?
Yep.
Um, wait, what's his name again?
Nikolai Zakhar.
I can spell it for you.
And I-K-O-L-I...
I got it.
Yeah?
Thank you.
Yeah, you see? Children.
Yeah. Vanya Zakharov.
It's me.
Oh, shit.
Oh, shit!
No. No way.
Yes, fucking way.
And I'm seeing him again tonight,
so I guess we have fun or something.
Yeah, whatever how fun you are, babe.
Uh, you wanna mind your fucking business?
You wanna mind your fucking business?
You're making it our fucking business.
Calm down, Diamond.
Chatty bitch.
Ginger cunt.
This pussy's illegal pussy on a watch this CIA married to the money keep my maiden name
Pussy drip, drip, drip, drop, let's Pussy slip, slip, twist, to your left, drop,
let's Pussy drip, pussy, pop, pop, pop, pop, let's
Pussy drip, drip, drip, drip, drip, drop, let's Pussy plush, teddy bear soft
Pussy kush, brother's flower Pussy wet, cuffed in a cock car
Pussy sick, pussy need a doctor Pussy perform, pussy needs an Oscar
Undefeated pussy is a boxer
If you want respect, girl, you eat the box first
Uh, broke it, trippin', trippin', trippin'
Uh, eat it, trippin', trippin', trippin'
Uh, gonna sip it, sip it, sip it, sip it
Uh, yeah
Pussy drip, I drip, I drip, drop, let's
Oh, it was crazy.
They put bonus, that's the deal, too.
Oh, yeah.
Well, let's go.
Oh, by the way, I have a party.
New Year's party.
You should come.
It's going to be banging.
I might have to work that night.
Oh, no, you might not work that night.
Bitch, what?
Can I bring someone?
No.
If it's a boy, no.
I don't want a sausage party.
No, she's not.
Okay.
See you here.
Why aren't you shooting?
I don't understand.
What?
You know,
you pay for an hour
and there's still like 45 minutes left
if you want to go again?
No fucking way.
Yes, fucking way.
I fucking told you, right?
I know.
Girl!
And it's fucking insane inside.
There's an elevator.
Oh, my God.
Fucking elevator.
Wait, never seen anything like it.
All right, take it off.
Come on, you two.
It's so amazing.
I mean, perfect.
Wait, am I tattooed?
No.
Bro.
I know.
I told you.
Didn't I tell you?
You're straight and upset.
What's up?
Oh, yeah.
Wow.
Oh.
Oh, hi, Lulu.
This is Eva.
Vodushka.
Yeah.
This is Lulu.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
I'm so excited that you are here.
And let's go drink.
Yes?
Yes.
Let's get some drinks.
Oh, yeah.
Are you ready?
And any jamal?
Yep.
Mmm.
Yo, that's a spleen that's eating Ivan.
Come on.
I'm going to make you some tea.
Good job, man.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Let's go.
Go, Marge.
There you go.
You can do it, Marge.
This is not jungle gym.
Good.
16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 25, 10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4,
Three, two, one!
Annie, Annie, Annie, let's go, let's go, let's go!
Give me five more shots!
Yeah!
I told you not to let the Armenians in.
I don't see anyone.
By the way, there is no coconut like this in Moscow.
Maybe.
Oh, I wanted to ask you.
Are you busy tonight?
Maybe.
What?
Well, it's New Year's.
So what?
I have holiday rates.
Let's go.
Oh!
Yeah?
Ivan, we're leaving.
Are you okay?
Fuck, dude, I'm busy.
What the fuck?
All good?
All great.
Oh, yeah.
Oh!
Fuck.
Oh, fuck.
Good morning.
No, no, dude, not good morning.
It is 5 o'clock p.m.
Then good evening.
Wait, are you leaving?
Yeah, don't go. Don't go yet.
No, dude, I have to go to work.
I have shit to do, okay?
But text me if you want to see me again, yeah?
What? No!
I have one question.
You have a question?
Yeah.
Okay, one minute.
One minute.
One minute, one question.
Yeah.
Like, how exclusive?
No, I don't know.
We can hang out with my boys.
My horny girlfriend for the week.
Oh, what about 10k of dollars?
15 cash up front.
Deal.
You know, I would have done it for ten.
Wow, you know, I wouldn't do it for less than $30,000.
Oh, my God!
Goodbye.
I
Thank you.
Tell him, because I don't want to.
I am going to fucking call him.
What's going on?
You don't even want to know, Jimmy.
She wants a week off.
I thought you wanted me to tell him.
You see the shit that I had to deal with?
I just made the schedule.
Now she wants to pull this bullshit.
Oh, the schedule.
We just gave you New Year's.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Jimmy, once you give me health insurance, workers' comp,
and a fucking 401K,
then you can tell me when I work and not work.
Well, none of that's going to happen, so...
Shocker.
Bye.
I'll be back on Tuesday.
Today is Tuesday.
Correct.
That's a week.
No shit.
Thank you.
Fuck.
You like that?
Yeah.
What's the matter?
You know, Annie, it's a champagne glass of my mother,
of my fucking mother.
And it will be your champagne glass.
And what we are drinking for?
What about my new girlfriend?
Hell yeah.
Two Anis.
Summer for you.
For you.
Okay, come on.
Summer for you.
One more, one more.
Okay, I'll put it in.
Instantly, instantly.
Oh.
Oh, my God.
Mm.
Oh.
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry, Ivan, not today.
It was really funny when Clara smoked last time my mother caught you in a cryo chamber.
What?
No, no, it's okay, it's okay, work.
You have a cryo chamber?
Yeah.
Oh, shit.
Oh shit.
Yeah, but I'm not allowed to drive them because my parents are dicks.
What's up?
What's up, man?
Welcome.
You guys can just eat whatever the fuck you want.
We got ice cream.
There's whatever the fuck these are.
There's Ring Pop.
Literally, I just fuck around here.
The boss is old as fuck and he's blind to death.
He can't even fucking hear us right now.
Helen Keller ass bitch.
Just fucking go crazy.
Yep, yep, yep.
Yep, ballinik sportivny.
What? Oh, come on, finish it off.
There we go.
Yes, I have a good piece.
You guys don't die on the job.
You're cool.
You watch this.
No, I'm not.
What time you guys have been told
there's no smoking dope in here?
But we're addicted to the reefer belly.
Come on, man.
We're gonna take our break. Ten minutes, man.
Hi, Mr. Billy.
Again, we're smoking dope.
Dope.
In your candy, chope. In your candy, chope.
What the fuck?
Shit!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
It's fucking cold!
What the fuck?
What are you doing?
Come back!
Can you say hi to my Instagram?
Hey.
Are you happy?
Yes, very happy.
Yeah, I'm always happy.
It's really good lines, but ladies first.
Ladies first.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Can you...
I'm on fire.
Guys, guys, do you know the best ketamine I've ever tried?
It was Vegas, I'm telling you.
Vegas? It's a great idea.
We are going to fucking Vegas!
Wow, I see the mirror, it's a fucking blue number.
How shameful I should be for him now.
Welcome to Vegas!
Welcome back, Mr. Zakharov.
Your suite is almost ready.
We didn't know you were coming, and the suite was occupied.
But they're out, and housekeeping should be done any minute.
What the fuck, man? Are you fucking kidding me?
You mean I have to wait?
You mean we have to wait right now, bro, yes?
Yes!
Go on, man.
I am fucking with you, dude.
We will stay here. It's nice to come back.
Very good.
Let's go up shit on this fucking castle.
in this fucking casino!
Have a great time.
What the fuck are we in for?
Yeah!
Whoa!
Come on!
Can somebody turn on music?
Turn on the music!
I got it, I got it.
Hey!
This one's mine!
Go away from my room!
You claim this room, I claim your sister.
I claim your mom.
If you are ready now, you can take some.
Okay, yes, I am ready now.
You should have been like that for sure.
We are going in all in.
Yeah, same. We are going all in.
Motherfucker.
Ooh, 22, I...
Whoa!
Whoa! Oh!
Whatever, whatever.
But do it with double dose because we're gonna go even harder tonight.
Okay?
Oh, shit!
I'm really happy that we are here and I don't know fuck you're the best guys
I'm fine.
Vanya, Vanya.
Vanya, Vanya, wait, wait, wait.
What's happening?
You know, it could last longer and be better if you just take it easy.
Like how?
Here, let me do it.
Ah.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, I think I love you.
Fuck.
I hope you had fun this week.
Oh, I did.
You know, we should do it again sometime.
Yeah, for sure.
But I have to go back to Russia because I promised my father that I would start working
in his fucking company.
Okay, so that's why you've been splashing out, hmm?
No, I'm always fighting like this.
I love it.
Well, I'm gonna miss you.
What?
Does that sound weird?
No, no. And will you miss me or my money, Blyat?
Well, your money, Blyat. Of course.
Yeah, I like it.
But if I get married to an American, I wouldn't have to go back to Russia.
Oh, yeah?
Mm-hmm.
Okay. So who'd you marry?
I don't know. Maybe crystals.
Or your friend Lulu. She's so hot.
You. You.
It's Vegas. It's fucking Vegas. Don't people get married in Vegas?
Don't fuck around.
I'm not fucking around.
Okay.
Okay, cool. Go get married.
Yes. Yes, let's get married.
You asshole.
Why?
Don't. Like, don't fucking cheese me with that shit, okay?
Stop.
It ain't cool.
Stop, stop, stop.
Annie.
Yeah?
Will you marry me?
Seriously?
Seriously.
Uh-huh.
So you marry me?
So you wanna get married to me, Vanya?
You want me to be your little wifey, yeah?
Yes.
I just think that we had great time together and...
Fuck, I'm nervous. I'll say it in Russian.
I think we would have a great time even if I didn't have money.
And I will become American and my parents will suck my dick.
Are you serious?
I'm serious.
And I said it
wisely.
Three carrots?
What about four?
Or five?
Or six?
honored to now pronounce you as husband and wife you may seal your father's
certificate
It's my wife! She can't do it! It's my wife, man!
The future is almost too far
Can you see it?
I'm fucking not gonna make it!
I am American, man!
Can you feel it now?
Can you feel it?
So this is for real?
Yeah, it's for real. What do you mean?
Cause if it is, I gotta stop letting the high rollers in. They're stealing my best curls.
Come here.
You're so lucky.
Oh, my God, I know. Thank you.
Yay!
You hit the lotto, bitch.
Girl power ball.
Oh, my God, are you gonna try?
Please stop. You don't...
You'll come over for dinner, right?
You know, I've been thinking about a honeymoon,
and I think we should do it at Disney World,
because that's been, like, my dream
since I've been a little girl.
Yeah. You know those suites
where it's, like, the Disney princess theme?
I'm Cinderella.
Yes, fucking Cinderella.
You know me so fucking well, babe.
Bye, Annie. You better visit us, bitch.
Oh, of course I will, Jenny.
Bye, babe.
Caught you well?
Seems I did, didn't I?
I give it two weeks, bitch.
Oh, Diamond.
Oh, sweetie.
You know, I really hope you find your happiness one day.
I hope you find a fucking plastic surgeon.
The fuck? Okay, Annie, Annie.
Play my fucking face again, bitch.
Stay jealous, babe. Stay jealous, honey.
Jealousy is a disease. Remember that, Diamond?
I'm just gonna go chill in my mansion or whatever.
You know, no big deal.
Shine a light on our greatest days
Light up, light up, light up
This day is light up, light up.
Oh, and the world comes alive.
And the world comes alive.
Oh, oh, oh, stay close to me.
Hold on, stay close to me.
Watch the world come alive tonight
Stay close to me
It's not about respect.
It's just gossip.
No, I'm going there now.
What did they say when you told them?
I don't want to really talk about them.
Well, you did tell them, right?
No.
That's it.
That's good, isn't it?
Parents want their children to get married.
Yes, but my parents are tired.
You know, whatever.
In any case, I hope they like the wine we met.
By the way, when will we meet your parents?
Are you making fun of me?
I'm trying here asshole. Yeah, no, yeah, I'm trying here asshole.
Yeah, no, you have a great Russian accent. You're better and better at it.
You're almost a speaker.
Oh, okay.
You're a liar.
No, no, no, not now, Annie. Not now.
I'm playing. I have a mission.
Give it back. Give it back.
I lost.
Stop.
Okay.
Arguments and facts put his photo as some chick during a basketball match.
They wrote that she's a prostitute.
Hey, this is not funny.
Don't laugh.
If it turns out to be true, then I'm a whore in shit.
Although, a whore in shit will be deeper than me.
But still.
Sounds like some kind of a goldfish.
Hey, is Ivan at the house?
I don't know.
He hasn't left since I've been here,
but I just started my shift.
Do you know if he got married?
Married? I've no idea. I just got here.
Okay, open the gate.
I'm expecting guests.
Oui.
Hello, what do you need?
Ivan, it's Garnik.
I got it. What do you need?
Ivan-chan, open the door please.
I'm busy. No.
We need to talk.
Why do you always have to repeat twice?
I'm busy. I have guests.
Ivan-chan, it's important. We need to talk.
That's it. Bye. Get the fuck out of here.
Who was that?
One of my father's monkeys.
Son of a bitch.
What the fuck?
Are you kidding me?
What are you doing?
You can't just walk into my house like that.
We need to talk.
Vanya, what the fuck?
Vanya, should I call 911?
No, like, it's okay, it's okay.
What?
Did you fall for her?
Yes!
Why did you turn your head?
I'm was crazy!
Did you find out about it by the signature?
It's a signature.
So you found out and now you're fucking with my son?
You have very big problems, bro!
You're gonna have big problems if you fucking kick my son's ass!
Daniel, what the fuck is going on?
I need to see... wait, is this a marriage license ban?
Are you crazy?
Bro, the sooner we do it, the sooner we get out of here.
My parents are fucking crazy.
Come on, open it, come on.
They want to prove it. I'll give them the proof.
Let's go.
All right.
I'm Igor.
You?
Annie.
I'm Vanya's wife.
Congratulations.
I'm bad.
Parents?
Toros.
No, you... you fucked?
No!
What the fuck is going on here?
I have no idea.
What are you doing?
That's it. Go, go, go.
Wait.
Go, Ivan, wait.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, it's okay.
Yeah? What the fuck is going on?
Yeah, just time to say goodbye to you guys.
Guys, my wife and I need some personal space.
You're tired. Go home, damn it.
You have to wait for Toros to answer.
And I have to wait for you, your Armenian ass,
to get the fuck out of my house.
Sorry.
So sorry. Excuse me.
Welcome, bro.
Ivan...
That's Toros.
Stand by.
What stand by?
He texted stand by, so we stand by.
So stand by outside my mansion, motherfucker.
Yeah.
It's a problem, fuck.
It turns out it's true.
Yes.
I saw their marriage license certificate.
Galya Stepan, I beg you, don't worry so much.
Ivan, with all due respect, your father sent us here.
Your fucking bullfrog sent you here, who works for me, who pays me money,
and you brought some fucking whore to my house.
Don't, I swear to you, we'll fix everything.
Galya Stepan, yes, Galya Stepan.
You will be fired from the face of the earth!
Bitch!
Arjan!
Look, look, you work for Ivan's family, so I'm assuming that means you work for him,
right?
So if he's telling you to take it outside, fucking take it outside.
Fucking take it outside!
Listen to my wife!
Real talk!
You, I give you!
Dog, yo!
Everybody's so sorry I have to go.
I have an emergency. Sorry about that.
Come on, come on, come on!
Come on, come on!
Wait, wait!
Toros is calling.
Hello, Toros?
Put me on a fucking speaker so this hooker can hear me too.
He just called me a hooker?
She's fucking erotic dancer. Hi, Doris!
What did you do, Ivan?
What did you do?
I've been spying on you for two weeks.
Two weeks.
And you married a prostitute?
Fuck your mother.
I'm not a fucking prostitute, you fucking piece of shit.
I'm a fucking Armenian piece of shit.
Are you Armenian piece of shit?
Can you imagine what a disgrace?
Fuck.
Doros.
My mother was scared.
Do you hear me?
Doros.
Your mother.
She never cried in her life.
She was crying on the phone.
No, Doros.
Shame on you.
Fuck you, fuck.
F-fuck!
Sonia, the fuck is going on?
Ivan, what the fuck? What does that mean?
Do you understand?
Game over for you. That's it.
Vanya, we are married. They're gonna have to accept that.
Yeah, I know.
Yes.
Accept that?
That's funny. Sure, yeah.
Ivan, listen to me carefully.
I'll be there in ten minutes.
Bitch!
You and your bitch are going with me.
Bitch?
You shluha?
Your mother is a fucking shluha!
Who the fuck is this guy?
Ten minutes, you hear me?
In ten minutes, both of you are coming with me down to the city hall.
We're gonna annul this marriage, you hear me?
This marriage is gonna be annulled!
Oh, I am not going fucking anywhere!
We are not getting a divorce because you tell us to!
Go fuck yourself!
You go fuck yourself!
Me go fuck myself, me fuck myself,
You go fuck yourself and your fucking mother, motherfucker!
Shut the fuck up! Shut the fuck up!
You don't even know who the fuck I am!
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop!
Torres, Torres, my parents are going to America right now.
Did I get that right?
Yes. Are you deaf?
They are leaving Russia in an hour.
Tomorrow noon we're going to go meet them.
You hear me?
What the fuck is going on?
Come on.
Come on, come on, come on.
Why do we have to leave the house?
They can't just fucking come in here like that.
Excuse me, get the fuck away from me, please.
Just use this minute, Toros.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Where are we going, Ivan?
I don't know where are we going, but we are going.
Where is he going?
We have to leave him.
Why are they staying?
That doesn't make any sense.
Ivan, where are you going?
We should call the fucking police or something.
Chanya?
Did he say he's leaving?
Ivan, we didn't...
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Hey, I need to get dressed, though.
My fucking clothes are upstairs.
Fuck!
Karnik, get him.
Karnik, Toros.
Where the fuck?
Wait, give me one half a minute.
Stop, stop, where are you going?
No, we have no time.
I have to get dressed, Ivan.
And I have no fucking hair.
Oh my God.
Okay, bye.
What the fuck?
Are you fucking kidding me?
Ivan!
Oh my fucking God.
Ivan, what the fuck?
Whoa.
Uh, uh, uh.
Get the fuck out of my way.
Baby!
Ivan!
Oh!
Get the fuck out of my fucking way, motherfucker.
What?
Do not fucking touch me.
No, no, no, no.
Stop!
Ivan! Ivan!
Relax, relax. It's okay.
You fucking relax!
What is happening?
Somebody talk to me, please!
You fucking motherfucker! What the fuck is wrong with you?
Relax.
Motherfucker!
Everything all right?
Why?
Stay the fuck back!
No, no, what?
No, no, no, no, no! Put it! It's a bad way!
Just see!
I fucking dare you!
No, I don't touch you.
No, no, no, no, no, no!
Don't leave. It's okay.
Just put it...
Whoa! Stop!
Please! Stop!
Stop, please!
No, no! Stop!
Don't... stop it.
Please!
Abby, what are you doing?
Are you killing her?
Stop it! Stop it!
I've been throwing another one of his tantrums, huh?
Caldwell, it's okay.
If you don't stop, I will tie you up!
You're not tying me up, motherfucker!
Get the fuck off me!
You are fucking insane!
Hey! Hey!
Help me! He's attacking me!
What the fuck are you doing to me, Brad?
Get the fuck off me! Somebody help!
Get off me!
You said you'd detain her. I detained her.
Yeah, but why did you detain her?
Because she fucked up here.
She got upset and started jumping around.
What was he supposed to do?
Igor, what the fuck are you doing, Brad?
Fuck, she fucked up my underpants.
No, no, no, no, please, please, please, no!
Let me go, you fucking asshole!
Goddamn fucking bastard!
Okay.
You crazy motherfucker!
You better stay the fuck away from me!
Stop, stop, you are not going anywhere.
Come back, please come.
She's gonna run away.
Come on.
Hey, stop!
Hold her!
You...
No!
You're not my mom!
Ah!
Put me down, motherfucker!
Fuck!
What, bro?
She's biting!
Fuck!
What?
What do you want?
Fuck!
Why?
No, no, no, don't. I don't even know what is going on here.
I didn't do anything. Don't tie me. I'm not gonna run.
I promise I'm calm. I'm not gonna do anything.
I'm not gonna run away.
You do not need to tie me.
No, you motherfucker. You don't need to tie me.
Come down. Listen, listen.
Ivan's father won this marriage annul.
You stay in here and get in this annul.
You heard my boss.
Fuck your boss.
Oh, fuck!
I just want to know what is going on!
Someone fucking tell me what's going on!
I'm not gonna run. Let me go!
Oh, God.
She broke my nose, I think.
Yeah. I'm glad I broke your fucking nose!
You fucking bitch! You broke my nose!
Yeah, next time I'll kick you in the fucking balls!
God, let me go!
God, are you fucking idiot? Talk to me!
You can untie me, motherfucker!
I am not fighting. I'm not gonna run. Just fucking untie me
Oh
You are so fucked
You're going to prison
Where is your eyes?
I can't wait until Ivan sees what you did to me.
Rich people don't have eyes.
Ivan did just leave the house.
He did not leave. He is going to get help.
I don't think so.
Garry!
Fucking asshole.
Yeah, I bet you like this, huh?
Yeah, you like this, you sick fuck!
I bet you get off on this.
Fucking psycho!
Thor, where are you?
Open the gate.
Open the gate!
Okay, sir, but Ivan just...
Open the fucking gate!
I am not fighting. Let me go.
No.
You are not going anywhere.
You two are fucking dead for this
Irony Bond fucking wife!
Vanya?
Oh.
Oh, are you the Armenian fuck I was talking to?
What the fuck is happening?
Is this the big fucking boss?
What happened here?
She happened.
Hey, mister, can you fucking tell this guy I don't want to tie me?
Yeah, she did this.
Hello?
Where's Ivan?
Ivan ran away.
Why the fuck does no one else?
Ran away?
Excuse me, sir.
I tried, but then there was ice on the floor.
I tried to stop him.
You tried?
You don't try.
You just grab the guy.
What do you mean you tried?
What do you mean?
I'm not allowed to touch that motherfucker.
Excuse me.
Shut the fuck up.
Don't you fucking let me go.
Tell this guy to fucking let me go.
Excuse me.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, fucking motherfuckers.
He doesn't answer.
What did I tell him?
Hey, fuckface!
I'm going to kill you.
Can you tell this motherfucker to let me go?
Why is she on top of you, man?
What's going on?
I don't know what's going on.
Can you please tell him to untie me?
Why is she on top of you?
I'm holding her.
Put her down, please.
No, don't do that.
Yes, fucking put me down.
Tell him to fucking put me down, please.
Put him down.
Why are you holding her like that?
No, no, no, be careful, bro.
Fuck!
Be careful.
Hey, now can you tell him to fucking untie me?
Why did you, why did, why did you tie her hands?
Untie me.
Luke!
Why, you afraid of this little girl?
Can you tell her to fucking untie me?
She's an animal.
She's a fucking little girl.
She'll, she'll beat you both up.
She's not fighting like one.
I'm gonna get my phone.
Can you untie her?
Yes, please.
This is ridiculous, man.
Untie her.
It's embarrassing.
She will start swinging again, doesn't it?
You can't get anything out of her.
She's uncontrollable.
Oh, fuck you.
She's an animal, bro.
No, these guys are fucking liars.
Listen to me. Where is your phone? Can you please give me your phone?
My phone is in the other room. I will go get my phone if you untie me.
I need you to untie me.
Which other room? Over there? Can you...
No, I will get my phone. I'll get my phone and I'll call you.
I will untie you. Give me a minute.
I just need your phone to call Ivan.
I know.
I will get my phone.
Let's just calm down for one second.
Be careful.
Calm down for a second.
I am calm. I'm not fucking moving.
Okay, look. We have an emergency here.
It's very important, okay?
I need you to cooperate. I'm begging you.
You guys came in here,
they chased Ivan out of the fucking house,
they fucking tied me, they attacked me,
that motherfucker was making me sit on his fucking lap.
You guys are fucking crazy.
I'm terribly sorry it went down that way, okay?
I'm terribly sorry.
But now we have to just call him, okay?
Here, help me, please.
He's on your phone?
Yeah, it's under husband.
Okay, yep, husband.
Here we go.
Please leave your message.
It goes to voicemail.
It's a fucking great husband you have.
First ditches you, now doesn't answer your calls.
Real marriage my ass, man.
Trava swamp.
Fuck you, swoleish malinky.
I don't know what kind of...
fucked up family shit is going on here,
but Ivana and I are married, okay?
This is a real marriage, and I'm not getting a divorce.
This is not a real marriage.
This is a real marriage.
Okay, and we're getting in an old,
and you have no say in it.
Well, I'm his fucking wife,
so I do think I have a say in it.
Absolutely not.
Listen to what I'm telling you.
You got married illegally.
It's a fraud marriage, and we're getting in an old.
A fraud marriage? S-A-P.
No, we are two consenting adults
who got married legally,
and there is nothing you can fucking do about it?
Nah, this is Ivan just fooling around with you.
Get over it.
You have no fucking idea.
Yo, yeah?
When did you guys meet, huh?
When did you meet him?
Strip club.
I am telling you, you do not know this guy.
I do know him.
You do not know this guy, I'm telling you.
I know my husband, I do.
No, you don't.
It's classic Ivan.
I've been dealing with his shit since he was six years old.
And now his parents are gonna kill me
and my fucking family will never talk to me again.
Fucking swolech malinki.
Fast mes.
I love my husband and I plan on being with him forever.
No, don't give me that bullshit.
Do not give me that bullshit you don't love him.
You do not love him and he doesn't love you.
You understand? That's in your head.
I can't wait to have Ivan's children.
In fact, I think I'm probably already pregnant.
I certainly hope you're lying,
because we're going to have to take care of that, too.
I promise you that.
Oh, the fuck you will.
Yes, we will.
And I would like all of you to fucking untie me and leave my home,
or I will be pressing charges.
Your home?
Yeah, my home.
This isn't Ivan's home.
This is his father's house.
Everything Ivan has belongs to his father, you understand?
Ivan has nothing.
You know that bedroom you've been fucking in?
That's his parents' room.
Do you know where's Ivan's room?
It's down the hall with fucking spaceships on the walls.
Do you know why?
Fucking tell me why.
You're already gonna tell me, sir.
Because he's a fucking child, that's why.
Fucking kid.
You don't understand.
He shamed his family by marrying somebody like you.
If you think for a second this is gonna be allowed,
you're dead wrong.
In fact, if you don't help me fix this,
Help me fix this, I'm gonna have you arrested.
Yeah.
I'm gonna have you arrested.
Arrested?
Yeah.
Oh, that's fucking hilarious.
Yup.
Arrested for what?
For what?
I'll tell you for what.
Trespassing?
Trespassing.
Fraud, cheating, theft.
Theft?
Yes, theft. Assault.
And actually the picture is very, very clear here.
A skimming prostitute married Yvonne,
cheated Ivan to marry her so she can steal from his wealthy family.
That's it.
Definitely.
And I'm sure you already have criminal records, so...
For sure, brother.
Yeah, one, two, three, you're in jail.
Easy.
Yep.
Ivan proposed to me.
He wanted to get married.
He put a fucking ring on my finger.
Do you see this shit?
What ring?
He bought me a fucking four-carat ring.
Does this look real to you, motherfucker?
Bet you never seen one of these before, have you, huh?
Uh, uh, .
No. No.
This is my fucking ring, Ivani.
Give me that fucking ring.
I am not giving you the fucking ring.
You touch me and I will fucking scream, motherfucker.
Do not come fucking here.
Get that fucking ring off of her.
Don't let her see you.
Be careful.
Hold her legs.
That was weird.
This is Zahara's property.
Fuck you!
Shut up. Shut up.
Run!
Hey, hey, don't scream.
Hey, what is she saying?
Shut up!
Shut the fuck up.
Is she saying rape?
Is she?
What?
Rape?
Shut up.
What are you doing?
Rape?
What rape?
What the fuck are you doing?
Hey, stop screaming.
Please stop screaming.
You get us in front of the police,
of that judge first thing in the morning or the family cuts ties with your firm. Simple
as that. No, no, no trying.
Everything will be okay.
Yeah.
Nothing.
You calm now?
You gonna behave?
Trust me, I know.
I know what you're thinking.
You're thinking this little shit betrayed you.
Well, guess what?
He betrayed me too.
Me too.
You see?
He betrayed all of us.
Because he's a spoiled brat that doesn't want to grow up.
Big time.
And now we're in this mess that we have to fix it together.
You understand?
But I'm going to help you.
Okay? I'm going to help you.
The way I see it, this is a green card marriage.
Therefore, Ivan owes you a green card marriage fee.
It's only fair.
So once this thing is annulled,
I'm going to make sure you get $10,000 fee in cash.
Hmm?
I'm going to bring this down, but no screaming, okay?
If you scream, this goes right back in.
You understand?
10K.
It's as good as you're gonna get here, honey.
What do you say?
I want to talk to Ivan before agreeing to any of this.
Sure, of course.
We all want to talk to Ivan.
We want the same thing.
Okay, so let's fucking find Ivan.
All right, but look at me.
Look at me.
Once we find Ivan, which we will,
and we get this thing annulled, which we will,
you're going to walk away with 10K fee
and never, ever contact Ivan again.
Is that understood?
Fine.
I'm tired.
Excuse me, I have to get dressed. Can I have some privacy, please?
Anora Mikheyeva?
Annie. It's Annie.
It says Anora.
I know, but I go by Annie. Thank you.
Okay, get in.
What, am I done?
What are you talking about? We won't find him until we find him. Sit down.
Wait, why is he getting back here?
I'm not sitting next to this fucking psychopath.
You are the fucking psychopath.
I don't want to fucking sit next to you.
I'm not getting back there with you.
Un-fucking-believable.
Clara, come here.
Tonya is a little dirtier than usual.
So you can get out of the interrogation.
Okay?
Yeah.
Come on.
I have no fucking idea.
You better be.
Okay, let's go.
I need to go to the hospital, Lope.
No.
No, you're okay.
Don't worry about it.
No, I'm not, bro.
I feel like I have a concussion or something.
Oh.
Sorry, Paul.
What?
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
What's happening?
Double.
I don't want you talking to me, okay?
My head is pounding, bro.
You can't even get a...
My God, we're gonna get into a fucking car accident.
Jesus, I know something.
What do you know about driving?
What do you know?
You shut the fuck up.
You've been bitching your mother this entire fucking car ride
about a little fucking scratch on her face.
You're the biggest fucking pussy I ever met.
What the fuck?
Okay, let's go. Doesn't matter. Let's go.
Let's go.
A little bit faster.
Hurry up.
Hey, Crystal.
Hey, Annie.
Hey, have you seen Vanya today?
No, why, is everything okay?
No, yeah, everything's fine.
Could you give him a call from me, please?
Okay, what's going on?
I just need you to call him.
Can you do me a favor and call him?
Don't ask too many questions.
Just pick up your phone and call him.
Okay, Tom?
Tom, Annie's here.
Hey, Tom? Hello?
Have you seen Ron yet today?
I have not, no.
Has he like texted or called you at all?
No, no, no, no.
Okay, could you just call him right now for me?
All right, these dudes.
It's fine, I just can't.
Wait, what's going on?
Why would I?
Just pick up your phone and call him.
I cannot call you.
Who are you?
It doesn't matter who I am. I just need you to call me.
It doesn't matter. I'm not gonna give you my fucking...
Listen, Ivan is in a lot of trouble. We need to find a way.
Hey, hey, one of you better get Ivan on the line now.
Fuck.
On the line. On the line.
What the fuck is funny?
What the fuck is funny, man? I'm telling you to call Ivan.
What is wrong with that?
Don't complicate your life, man. I'm gonna come back there and just gonna fucking...
I'll get you in your fucking line, you motherfucker.
That's not a good idea. That is not a good idea.
Get the fuck out of here.
What's up, man?
I told you it's a fucking bad idea.
So pick up your phone and call it now.
Whoa, whoa. Fuck off!
Llamay vsev, na hul, blyat.
What the fuck?
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck!
Fucking call Ivan now!
Okay, okay, this is Parker!
That's crazy.
Oh, fuck!
Put it on speaker.
I am so sorry.
I am so fucked. Put it on speaker.
I am so fucked.
Where's your phone?
Hold on, man. Just don't break anything, all right?
Call him. Put it on speaker.
There you go. There you go.
He's not gonna answer the phone.
He's not gonna answer. I know.
I know he's not gonna fucking answer.
Where's his other friends?
Is he with Alex?
Alex is working right now. He can't be without Alex.
Where is he working?
Totiana's.
Let's go.
What the hell
Where you going the car it's five minute walk no
Parking come on. Let's go. Why don't we walk?
That took way fucking longer than five minutes.
Hey. Table for four?
Alex, this? Alex.
Alex?
Robotik, I'm saying.
Varyonok?
Yeah. Let's go.
No, wait. Hold on. You guys didn't go there.
No, you're good. You're good.
I just matched the dealer. Just one more second.
Oh, my God, Alex. Have you seen Vanya?
No. What's going on?
I'm looking for Vanya. It's a family emergency.
Have you seen Ivan?
What's going on?
No!
You're good.
Don't worry.
Don't worry about it.
Can you call him, please?
I haven't seen him.
Call him?
Really?
Just call him.
Yes, please call him.
Call him.
Are you an actress?
I saw you somewhere.
No?
I just found out.
No, you look good.
No.
Give me your phone one second.
One second.
I'm fine.
Have you talked to him today?
No, I haven't seen him.
Okay.
You gotta have your husband's photo on your phone.
No, I'm not giving you my fucking phone again.
I need your phone for one second.
I just need this phone.
And you know what? If you touch me again,
I will fucking scream.
Yeah, he buys me his Instagram too.
I don't have Instagram. I'm an adult, man.
What are you talking about?
You're going to cost me my job here.
Yes, yes. Nice.
Nice. Oh, okay.
Well, look, he's Trevano. We don't know where he is.
What?
He's like a fucking fiend.
Okay, thank you.
Where...
Where are you going?
I'm going to see a new musician.
Do you think that he would be with Dasha?
Not unless he's in Bahamas with her and her new fuckboy.
Cut the music, man. Cut the music.
I will be very grateful to you.
We pay, and he wants attention.
I beg your pardon.
It's just a sick child.
If you know, let me know.
I haven't seen him.
I need a cigarette.
I'm having fun.
I'm thirsty.
We'll get cold if you don't cover your neck.
Why did you bring that?
Why the fuck did you bring that?
Why, so you could fucking gag me again?
Motherfucker.
Fuck it. Give me the scarf.
No! No! No!
Why border sadafada?
Hey! Hey!
This is my car! No, no, no, no, no, no!
No, no, no!
It's already attached. It's already attached.
I gotta take it. I gotta take it.
You can't take my car.
This is life and death situation.
Hey, you jerk-ball!
You were parked in the middle of the fucking street, okay?
My friend, I was just parking.
There is no sign.
I'll give you money. How much?
How much?
Listen to me.
100, 200, 300, tell me.
Listen, down at the yard, you're gonna talk to the people, okay?
You're gonna talk to the people.
Fuck you, Dan.
Fuck you.
What do you mean, fuck me?
What do you mean, you're gonna talk to the people?
I don't give a shit.
Get the fuck out my way.
You're gonna have to fucking talk.
You fucking asshole, dude.
I've been on the job two fucking weeks, bro.
What the fuck are you?
Are you fucking kidding?
You're kidding me.
You're just crazy.
Oh my fucking God.
It's all because of you.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
You're a fucking cunt.
Oh my fucking God.
It's all because of you.
You are, come on.
I have your license plate and you get that car, you're all fucked.
Yo, yo, yo, yo, yo.
What the fuck are you doing?
Fuck you Russians.
God, Jesus Christ, you guys are fucking crazy.
We'll find this fucker even if it takes all fucking night.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
You're sorry, Laura.
This is okay.
Come on, give me something.
I don't know, I don't know.
Think, think. Where?
Gaming. He likes video games.
Maybe he'll be at an arcade or something.
I don't know.
Don't be a fool, Miki.
You're a real champion.
Guys, I haven't seen this guy today.
No one.
Have we seen Ivan Zakharov?
No, not yet.
Guys, have you seen this guy today?
Oh, billiard hall! There is the billiard hall!
Remember five years ago we...
You were teaching him how to play billiard.
We played here, right here around the corner.
You remember? Five years ago?
I remember.
Come, come, one second, my friend.
Look at this picture. Have you seen this guy?
Ivan, Ivan. Is that Ivan?
Have you seen him today?
No, not today.
He does the greatest parties.
He's really cool.
Guys, have you seen this guy?
He's been missing.
You sure?
Wait, I'll ask him.
No, no, stop, stop.
Guys, have you seen this guy today?
Think, think, think, think.
And can you keep calling him, please?
Oh, my God.
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
Do you understand that my wife has to drive this car tomorrow?
Do you?
I'm not getting back in there.
Still fucking stinks in here.
Fuck, I know. Shit!
Which clubs did you go with him?
I don't know. We went to a lot.
I don't know. We went to a lot of them.
Take me to every single one.
Hey, have you seen this guy today?
Yeah, we're talking about George Mason.
Where?
Like 20 minutes ago.
He just left.
Have you guys seen this guy today?
Yes?
Did you look for Ivan Sakharov?
Yes, I did.
He left me an account of $800.
Where is he now?
I don't know. I need him to pay.
Okay, bye.
No, wait, but you know him?
I told him my apologies. You can tell him one more time.
I'm gonna definitely make them up to you.
Or up to them. Or up to you.
What can I do?
What do you want me to do?
He's fine.
Is it a real mink?
No.
Oh.
It looks like real mink.
Yeah, it's fucking real, but it's not mink. It's fucking Russian sable, okay? Which is worth a lot more than mink.
Of course I'm ashamed.
But don't talk about that baby.
I just want to ask a question.
Have you seen this guy?
He was here half an hour ago.
He was drunk. We didn't let him in.
Where did he go?
I don't know.
I'm going to the bathroom.
I'm so fucked.
So fucked!
You know, he fucked me much harder than he fucked you.
Oh, yeah? 100%.
Trust me.
If we haven't found him by now, we are not finding him.
Did I ask you? Did I ask you?
Give your opinion to yourself.
I'm gonna give your opinion to yourself
And I'm gonna give them some
Vanya
Yeah, you know it's so sad that marriage must really be in the toilet already Vanya's here
Excuse!
Have you seen this guy today?
How about you, sir?
Igor, thank you for the tablet.
I want what he had.
I want one of those.
Did you fucking hear me?
You want one of those?
No.
No? What the fuck why?
Because I don't deal drugs.
A fucking gopnik who can afford to live in Brightwater and doesn't deal drugs?
You're right.
It's my grandmother's apartment and it's called Rats.
I don't have any more, and I'm not groping.
You're right.
A fatty ass bitch is what you want.
Hey guys, have you seen this guy today?
No, no, no.
What's a fatty ass bitch?
.
Yep, what he said.
Why are you so rude? I have questions for you.
I mean, honestly, come on, what the fuck is wrong with you, huh?
No work ethics, lazy, stupid.
I don't understand.
I've been working since I'm 16 years old.
What is wrong with you?
All you do is tic-tac Instagram, tic-tac Instagram.
That's it.
He's on HQ.
What?
Fucking headquarters.
Hello.
What's the address?
West 38th Street.
I fucking love that place.
Yeah, but...
Oh, my fucking God.
Guys, a little bit.
Hurry up.
Hey, you guys.
Toros.
That's 45 minutes away.
Hurry up.
You're Vanya, right?
Yeah, that's me.
Anora.
It's not Anora.
It's Annie.
Tell your friend to hold him there at any cost.
Even if they have to physically hold him, like grab him really.
I said go girl, feel bad, feel bad, go.
Little Sally walker on, shake your popper on, bend it over, make it wobble on.
Got a lot of bones, pick it up and drop it on.
For the proper friends and the baby.
They have the best skin they ever died.
Add that shit up just like mathematics, if you do it for freedom it's ass backers.
All of you bitches is mad at me, probably mad cause you ain't in my tax bracket.
I love you. I love you.
Shut up.
Blah, blah, blah.
Don't have a heart attack, but Bonnie's upstairs in a private with diamonds.
Annie, who the hell are these guys?
Daddy is fucked.
I feel daddy is fucked.
Whipping in a pink truck.
Daddy is fucked.
He want to get in my guts.
Licking my quits how I'm up.
Daddy is fucked.
I feel daddy is fucked.
Fucking daddy is fucked.
Vanya!
He read the bust.
I feel daddy is fucked.
Wait, he's in one of these rooms?
Yeah.
Daddy is fucked.
Shit, I'm sorry.
I feel daddy is fucked.
Sorry.
I'm very sorry, Daisy.
What?
I feel daddy is fucked.
Carly, you seen Diamond?
I think she's in the pool room.
Hey, let's go.
Where's Paul?
The whole room.
I feel daddy is fucked.
I feel deadiest fuck, I feel, I feel, I feel
I feel like I'm gonna be dead
Oh, what the fuck?
Get the fuck off my fucking husband!
Are you fucking mad?
Yeah, I am about to be fucking mad, bitch!
Let's go!
Oh, you wanna fucking go, bitch?
I'm like, come get you, son of a bitch!
I've been fucking calling you,
why haven't you answered any of my fucking calls?
You little son of a bitch!
Why'd you fucking leave me, Vanya?
I tried to run after you.
These guys, they fucking tied my wrists up.
They took my ring.
Forward, bro.
They fucking assaulted me.
That guy fucking assaulted me.
You can call in the car. Get up.
I fucking found him, so I get to fucking talk to him, OK?
That was the deal.
Vanya, our hour's not over.
Oh, get her the fuck out of here.
Get the fuck out of my private, bitch.
Wow.
Vanya, look at me.
Real fucking fat bitch.
I need you.
You diamond.
This is very important.
Vanya, look at me.
Just listen to me, baby.
Listen, these guys, they want us to get a divorce, okay?
It's not divorce. I told you a hundred times.
It's annulment. Annulment.
Vanya, tell them that we're not going to get a divorce, okay?
Tell them that this is a mistake.
Maybe this is very important.
Listen to me. Your parents are coming at 12 o'clock.
I helped you find them, so let me fucking 12 o'clock.
Just look at me, okay?
Fucking ignore them. It doesn't fucking matter about her.
It doesn't matter about anything, okay?
Just, I need you to tell them.
Vanya, this is not funny.
I know.
Vanya, look at me, baby.
Let's stay married, okay?
You know these guys? Yeah, I love them.
I love them.
Jesus, Vanya!
We have to talk about this, okay?
This is very, very important, all right?
I don't want to talk about this right now.
Just look what he's done.
No, no, no, Vanya, we can't drink right now.
You need to tell them.
Guys, he's fucking drunk. We can't talk right now.
Not fucking done talking.
Let's talk to him.
We're fucking living.
Vanya!
I know we're the only one around
Vanya, we have to keep talking about this
Viva la viola, viva la viola
Vanya, you're not fucking telling me this
Vanya, we're not talking about this
I'm trying to bring the spirit to voice
We can't go, okay, okay
You're not fucking the fuck out of my fucking face
Jimmy, Annie's here with three guys causing a scene
Russian Annie?
Let's go
I fucking told you
Get the fuck out of my fucking mind!
Two weeks, motherfucking no!
Fuck one, bitch!
Fuck one! Fuck one!
Guys, there's a fucking fight!
No way!
Shit! Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
Get out of here!
Get out! Get out!
Get out!
Get the fuck out of here!
Go! Go!
We fucking found you!
We found you!
I can't believe you went running
like a fucking baby.
But it's okay. Your parents are coming.
I mean, you're gone. You're gone, finally.
Fucking gone.
Vanya, do you know what's happening right now?
Do you fucking know what's going on right now, Vanya?
Get off me, man.
It's fucking wasted.
I need to talk to him when he's fucking sober.
I can't talk to him like this.
Talking is done.
Talking is not done.
Of course he's gonna do anything you say.
He's fucking plastered.
Talking is done.
Now we're gonna get this thing done in three hours.
Yes, he was.
Oh, slut, I'm gonna get sick.
You're gonna get this thing done.
You're gonna get your fucking money and you're gonna walk away.
That's it. That was the deal.
But, you know, you must really hate me, man.
I mean, seriously.
You know, after all I've done for you,
you know, everything...
I mean, I bailed you out how many times?
Huh? How many times?
And you do this to me.
You know, it makes me upset.
You know how embarrassing that is for me?
Huh?
Are you even listening to what I'm saying?
He's passed out, bud.
Now we wait.
I'm sorry.
Okay, he's here. Hey, wake up! Wake up!
He's here. Let's go.
I want to stay in the car.
Vanya, Vanya, look at me.
We need to talk before you go in there.
Vanya.
Vanya, don't say anything when you go in there, okay?
Vanya, I'm gonna handle this, okay?
Handle what? Don't talk to me.
None of your fucking business.
Let's go. Hello, everyone.
How are you, sir?
Oh, whoa, is he all right there?
Does he fucking look all right to you?
He is not fucking all right. He can barely stand.
How are you?
Fine, thanks.
Uh, the judge is being very kind, and he bumped us up.
Good.
Hello, Ivan.
I see.
Tired.
And this is the...
The lucky lady.
Okay. And who is this?
Him we're gonna meet.
I just hold him.
Okay, I don't know what that means and I don't wanna know.
Let's go. Get your IDs ready.
I talked to him.
He demands that it be done.
And he knows that his son is drunk.
He's not drunk, I told you. He just woke up.
Toros, please, come on, man. I'm not gonna risk my license because you can't...
You wanna keep working for the Zakharov family or not?
Mr. Sarnoff, you see yourself very fortunate.
We have a light calendar today, so, um,
what's your urgent matter?
Your Honor, we are here to file a complaint
and request for an immediate annulment
of a union that took place under duress.
Ivan Zaharoff and Anora Mihajlo...
Duress? My fucking ass.
Whoa!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Your Honor, but this is bullshit.
It's bullshit. These men are trying to...
Stop. You can't talk.
Okay, I'm sorry. They're trying to...
Do not fucking touch me.
Who's this man in the camel coat?
Security, please get this man away from me.
Mr. Shawna, is he with you?
Get him away from me.
Officer, take him back to the scene.
Thank you, officer. I appreciate it.
And thank you, Your Honor. I really appreciate it.
You're welcome. Keep that tone. You're welcome.
Your Honor, clearly, my husband is intoxicated right now.
Your Honor, objection.
She shouldn't be talking, sir.
Don't listen to her, please.
Sit down.
Why is she talking?
Your Honor, I apologize.
Please.
What I have been trying to explain to you,
we got married legally.
Objection, Your Honor.
They're not legally married, and she shouldn't be talking.
I want my answer now.
Your Honor, my apologies.
I apologize.
My client doesn't know what she's saying.
I'm sorry.
I am intoxicated.
Sit quietly.
We are legally married.
at a legitimate marriage place in Las Vegas, Nevada.
It is real. We have a marriage certificate.
We're not going to be signing it.
He got married in Nevada?
So what?
We can't annul it. It's here.
What?
We can fill in the divorce papers here.
If you want to speed up the process,
you have to go there.
Are you fucking kidding me?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Officer, get him off the table before he throws up.
Fuck!
Get him off the table.
Get him out.
Fuck!
Everyone out of the car.
Clear the court, officer.
Officer, clear the court, please.
Why did you go to Vegas?
Why not here in New York?
Can you explain to me?
We got fucking married in Vegas because that's
what he proposed to me.
So now we're going to go see your parents.
You're going to explain to them that you went to Vegas
without my permission.
You understand?
Because it wasn't my fault.
You too.
You're gonna have to tell them that you've taken to Vegas without my permission.
This is not my fault.
Get in the car!
I'm not getting in the fucking car because we're fucking done here
and I want my fucking ring now, motherfucker!
Vanya, you don't have to get...
Vanya, get out of the car, okay?
You do not have to listen to these people.
You don't have to listen to them because you're an adult, Vanya.
You're an adult, okay?
.
You're a good boy.
Okay.
Alright. We'll talk to your parents, okay?
We're gonna talk to your parents and they're gonna understand
because they love you.
They love you and they're gonna understand, okay?
Vanya, okay?
Right? Right?
They're gonna understand, right?
Get in the car.
Get in the car!
Right, Vanya?
Right?
Get in the car.
I want him clean and presentable in ten minutes.
And you behave.
Volna.
and he pours 4 pounds of this Kool-Aid into the pool.
The whole system of the woman is fucked up.
87 thousand dollars of opium.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
Showtime.
Nikolay, how did you get here?
How did you get up there?
Nikolay, I have bad news.
Tell me.
You won't like it.
I don't like it anymore.
Well?
What?
Vanya!
What's wrong with you?
Wait, look at me, Vanya.
Are you drunk?
Your mother is drunk. Gargoyle is drunk.
Yes, Galina Stepanovna, he is sober.
But it's not our fault.
Mom, I understand everything, but I'm ashamed.
You're ashamed?
Yes.
Why are you ashamed? You've disgraced our family and the whole world.
Galina Zaharova.
My name is Nora.
I'm very happy to finally meet you.
It's such an honor to be Ivan's wife.
And to be part of your family.
Ivan is not your husband.
And you are not part of this family.
And your Russian is embarrassing.
You have a new colleague?
Ma'am.
Ma'am?
Yes?
Vanya and I, we are in love, and we would like you to accept that.
Vanya is not in love with you.
Understand?
And we will not accept it.
Okay?
Vanya.
Torres wants to tell you something.
Fuck.
You are all idiots.
Vanya, we cannot get on the fucking plane right now.
I'm gonna discuss your future in our company.
Yes, Nancy.
Vanya, why are you listening to your fucking parents?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Vanya, we have to talk right fucking now, okay?
Vanya, we have to fucking talk.
No, no, no, no, go back to the plane.
Vanya, fucking look at me, Vanya.
Vanya.
Be a fucking man and talk to me.
I think the butterfly is bound to be with us.
Yes, they are both sides.
They are present.
You get it?
So we're getting a divorce. You...
Of course! Are you stupid?
Ivan! Hurry up!
Just a second!
And thank you...
For making my last trip to America so fun.
Yeah, you had fun?
Yeah. Let's go.
I don't know.
Where is it?
You are getting on this plane and you are getting divorce.
Yeah, we're gonna get a fucking divorce, but first I'm getting a lawyer.
Then I'm gonna sue Ivan and you and I'm gonna walk away with fucking half because I didn't sign a prenup.
Do that and you will lose everything.
Any money you may have, although I doubt you have much, will be gone.
Do you have a house?
Do you have a car?
All gone.
Your life and the lives of your family and friends, everything will be destroyed.
Thank you for trusting me and Tosu.
Your man's got married.
I don't think that's possible.
It's not.
Then what kind of freedom are we talking about?
What kind of freedom if I can marry a man?
Listen.
I'm sorry, I just wanted to use this moment to thank you.
We have a family council. Please, don't interfere.
You think it's normal?
Everything that happened is normal? How did you get to Vegas?
I don't understand.
How did you get there?
I understand and forgive you what you did.
Great.
I'm so grateful for your forgiveness.
Problema not you see me you know, but yeah, yeah, okay
Fucking glad to be divorced and you're sorry. Yes. Well fucking pathetic man. Are you seriously?
Pathetic motherfucker
Fucking pathetic your pathetic motherfucker
I'm just going to need some signatures if I could just get that back from you.
Actually, if I could just hang on to all, could I just thank you?
Okay, question.
Okay, yes, of course.
What does it mean?
You don't need to worry about that.
That's for the judge.
Are you sure?
Very sure.
Okay, so we're just going to need some signatures here.
So there you go.
And this one will be for, sorry, I'm going to mispronounce your name.
So Anora McKeever, I just need your signature as well.
Thank you. Um, oh.
Where the red box is.
Sign, please.
And then, oh, sorry, just one more.
Can I have my ID?
You can.
All right, let's go.
I understand that it's not going to be a topic right now,
but I think it would be right for Ivan to apologize.
Galina Stepanovna, don't pay attention to him.
He's just tired and drank on his hungry stomach on the plane.
He helped us all night.
So, my son won't apologize to anyone here.
Is that clear?
Of course not.
Let's go.
Yeah. Now your family is fucking trash.
Is this my scarf?
Yeah, you want...
Yeah, go get your little scarf, sweetie.
That's enough. Let's go.
Oh, I'm leaving. I'm leaving.
You know what? It's more fun.
Why don't you take your fucking coat, too?
That's enough. Let's go.
Thank you so much, ma'am.
You're very welcome.
Goodbye, America.
Okay.
It's for you.
Present.
Oh, gosh, no, I couldn't.
Thank you so...
Wait, is this real?
Take them to McCarran Airport.
Domestic.
Igor is gonna take you back.
You can stay in the house tonight,
but you gotta be out of there in the morning.
And he'll pay you when the bank opens.
Go.
And thank you.
and it is starting to stick as well we'll show you a live look at the roads in a little bit
but officials that we've talked with today say they are ready for whatever mother nature brings
the next few days we've got thousands of sanitation problems and zips that's coming
into an overtime tonight if it accumulates we'll be clearing snow and ice from the street
every highway every bike lane in this city will be out starting on midnight shift tonight
I had a birthday today.
Huh?
Was today your birthday?
No.
Yesterday was my birthday.
Yesterday was your fucking birthday?
I was 13.
Yeah.
Happy fucking birthday, I guess.
Thank you.
I like Anora.
I mean, I like Anora more than any.
Okay.
Says the fuckhead name Eager.
Fucking Eager.
Stupid name.
No, it's a good name.
It means barrier, warrior.
Yeah?
Eager means hunchback weirdo, you fucking piece of shit.
Can you shut the fuck up, please?
Touche.
Touche?
Touche, motherfucker.
You know, you really should try learning English
before attempting French.
Okay, touche.
Yeah.
and even your children's education were safe in the hands of...
And your name is better.
No.
But what does it mean?
...a snarled one, two and three train service a day,
federal investigators say...
In America, we don't care about that kind of stuff.
We don't give meaning to names.
It's... it's nothing.
...a transit team with Mitch Bailey
says the NTSB's preliminary report
is a factual rendition that is beyond dispute.
It's a factual rendition that is beyond dispute.
The question remains whether the problem January 4th
was with the radios themselves or human error.
Bailey says the radios were working back then.
There are multiple channels.
That's another question, you know.
They're all the same channel.
So I think we need to continue to look at those as possibilities.
But as I said, we're going to look both at not only the conduct of the individuals
to see if...
So it means...
One grand fruit, light...
I'm not interested in conversation, dude.
And bright.
It's good that you're not part of this family.
at the end of the 96th Street station platform,
and the collision occurred.
Did I ask for your fucking opinion?
No.
Exactly.
I just tried to support you.
Get the train out of the way
and to get it out of the way for rush hour, so...
Support me?
Dude, you fucking assaulted me.
You fucking support...
No, you...
No, I didn't assault you.
You didn't... You don't call that assault?
No?
No.
No, you're right. It's fucking battery,
as well as kidnapping,
and fucking a million other felonies, I'm sure.
Fuck you, dude.
But I didn't attack you.
I tried to calm you down so you wouldn't kill yourself.
I mean crazy too
but I can say
you're too crazy too
it's not funny
yeah
touche
but anyway you were
not in danger of
injury or
harm right
You know, if Garnet wasn't there, you'd have raped me.
Guaranteed.
Raped?
No doubt.
What? Why would I have raped you?
You have rape eyes
Right dice rape eyes
You heard me you sick motherfucker would have raped me
Okay, but I didn't want to rape you
Who yeah
Why
What?
Why?
What why?
Why wouldn't you have raped me?
Because I'm...
not a rapist.
Nope.
Because you're a faggot-ass bitch.
But the wind kicks up again tomorrow afternoon.
So how much do we expect?
About three to four in and around the city.
The three from the city on south in this area
is the one, the further northern end of that band.
The central forces of New Jersey, Middlesex County,
Monmouth County...
Here.
But here's the stadium series tomorrow night...
Good night.
Bundle up, gang. It's gonna be cold.
Temperature's dropping.
The wind chills make it feel even colder.
It's an afternoon game on Tuesday for the Rangers and the Islanders,
going at it probably in the upper 30s to about 40 degrees with a partly cloudy sky.
Hopefully you're sitting in the sun.
I'm sorry.
Hey.
Don't tell tourists.
This car is very you.
Do you like it?
No.
It's my grandmother's.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
Thank you.
you